<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Thrifty</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="this_is_sample_text">\t\t\t\t Water Jetpack Fort Myers and Naples
        area this week! Bringing out the pack today check it out! Beat the heat with
        some wakeboarding and water jetpacks! We guarantee you fly your first time!
        Flyboard World Cup Qualifier at Sugden Park in Naples, Florida was Awesome!
        It\'s only going to get better, 2 more days to go. Here\'s a couple shots of
        the action. This is some sample text and some more sample text after that. This
        is some sample text and some more sample text after that. This is some sample
        text and some more sample text after that. This is some sample text and some more
        sample text after that. This is some sample text and some more sample text after
        that. This is some sample text and some more sample text after that. This is some
        sample text and some more sample text after that. This is some sample text and
        some more sample text after that. This is some sample text and some more sample
        text after that. This is some sample text and some more sample text after that.
        This is some sample text and some more sample text after that. This is some sample
        text and some more sample text after that. This is some sample text and some more
        sample text after that. This is some sample text and some more sample text after
        that. This is some sample text and some more sample text after that. This is some
        sample text and some more sample text after that. This is some sample text and some
        more sample text after that. This is some sample text and some more sample text
        after that.  </string>

    <string name="txt_take_survey">Please take a short survey in order to show you customized
        content that aligns more with your interests: </string>

    <string name="txt_login_prompt">Would you like to register or login with an existing Thrifty account or login with
        your social media account? You may also choose to continue as a guest. </string>

</resources>
